[
    {
        "category": "Sports",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "At%20which%20bridge%20does%20the%20annual%20Oxford%20and%20Cambridge%20boat%20race%20start%3F",
        "correct_answer": "Putney",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Hammersmith",
            "Vauxhall%20",
            "Battersea"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Sports",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "With%20which%20team%20did%20Michael%20Schumacher%20make%20his%20Formula%20One%20debut%20at%20the%201991%20Belgian%20Grand%20Prix%3F",
        "correct_answer": "Jordan",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Benetton",
            "Ferrari",
            "Mercedes"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Sports",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Which%20German%20sportswear%20company%27s%20logo%20is%20the%20%27Formstripe%27%3F",
        "correct_answer": "Puma",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Nike",
            "Adidas",
            "Reebok"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Sports",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "What%20cricketing%20term%20denotes%20a%20batsman%20being%20dismissed%20with%20a%20score%20of%20zero%3F",
        "correct_answer": "Duck",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Bye",
            "Beamer",
            "Carry"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Sports",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Which%20of%20these%20teams%20isn%27t%20a%20member%20of%20the%20NHL%27s%20%22Original%20Six%22%20era%3F",
        "correct_answer": "Philadelphia%20Flyers",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "New%20York%20Rangers",
            "Toronto%20Maple%20Leafs",
            "Boston%20Bruins"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Sports",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "What%20is%20the%20nickname%20of%20Northampton%20town%27s%20rugby%20union%20club%3F",
        "correct_answer": "Saints",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Harlequins",
            "Saracens",
            "Wasps"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Sports",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "A%20stimpmeter%20measures%20the%20speed%20of%20a%20ball%20over%20what%20surface%3F",
        "correct_answer": "Golf%20Putting%20Green",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "%20Football%20Pitch",
            "Cricket%20Outfield",
            "Pinball%20Table"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Sports",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Which%20Formula%20One%20driver%20was%20nicknamed%20%27The%20Professor%27%3F",
        "correct_answer": "Alain%20Prost",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Ayrton%20Senna",
            "Niki%20Lauda",
            "Emerson%20Fittipaldi"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Sports",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "How%20many%20scoring%20zones%20are%20there%20on%20a%20conventional%20dart%20board%3F",
        "correct_answer": "82",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "62",
            "42",
            "102"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Sports",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "In%20a%20game%20of%20snooker%2C%20what%20colour%20ball%20is%20worth%203%20points%3F",
        "correct_answer": "Green",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Yellow",
            "Brown",
            "Blue"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Sports",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Which%20nation%20hosted%20the%20FIFA%20World%20Cup%20in%202006%3F",
        "correct_answer": "Germany",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "United%20Kingdom",
            "Brazil",
            "South%20Africa"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Sports",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "The%20F1%20season%20of%201994%20is%20remembered%20for%20what%20tragic%20event%3F",
        "correct_answer": "Death%20of%20Ayrton%20Senna%20%28San%20Marino%29",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "The%20Showdown%20%28Australia%29",
            "Verstappen%20on%20Fire%20%28Germany%29",
            "Schumacher%27s%20Ban%20%28Britain%29"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Sports",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "What%20is%20the%20highest%20belt%20you%20can%20get%20in%20Taekwondo%3F",
        "correct_answer": "Black",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "White",
            "Red",
            "Green"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Sports",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Which%20country%20is%20hosting%20the%202022%20FIFA%20World%20Cup%3F",
        "correct_answer": "Qatar",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Uganda",
            "Vietnam",
            "Bolivia"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Sports",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Which%20team%20was%20the%202015-2016%20NBA%20Champions%3F",
        "correct_answer": "Cleveland%20Cavaliers",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Golden%20State%20Warriors",
            "Toronto%20Raptors",
            "Oklahoma%20City%20Thunders"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Sports",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Which%20team%20was%20the%202014-2015%20NBA%20Champions%3F",
        "correct_answer": "Golden%20State%20Warriors",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Cleveland%20Cavaliers",
            "Houston%20Rockets",
            "Atlanta%20Hawks"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Sports",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Josh%20Mansour%20is%20part%20of%20what%20NRL%20team%3F",
        "correct_answer": "Penrith%20Panthers",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Melbourne%20Storm",
            "Sydney%20Roosters",
            "North%20Queensland%20Cowboys"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Sports",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Which%20car%20manufacturer%20won%20the%202016%2024%20Hours%20of%20Le%20Mans%3F",
        "correct_answer": "Porsche",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Toyota",
            "Audi",
            "Ferrari"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Sports",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Which%20soccer%20team%20won%20the%20Copa%20Am%C3%A9rica%202015%20Championship%20%3F",
        "correct_answer": "Chile",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Argentina",
            "Brazil",
            "Paraguay"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Sports",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "What%20national%20team%20won%20the%202016%20edition%20of%20UEFA%20European%20Championship%3F",
        "correct_answer": "Portugal",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "France",
            "Germany",
            "England"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Sports",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "In%202016%2C%20who%20won%20the%20Formula%201%20World%20Constructor%27s%20Championship%20for%20the%20third%20time%20in%20a%20row%3F",
        "correct_answer": "Mercedes-AMG%20Petronas",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Scuderia%20Ferrari",
            "McLaren%20Honda",
            "Red%20Bull%20Racing%20Renault"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Sports",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "What%20is%20the%20oldest%20team%20in%20the%20NFL%3F",
        "correct_answer": "Arizona%20Cardinals",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Chicago%20Bears",
            "Green%20Bay%20Packers",
            "New%20York%20Giants"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Sports",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "What%20is%20the%20oldest%20team%20in%20Major%20League%20Baseball%3F",
        "correct_answer": "Atlanta%20Braves",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Chicago%20Cubs",
            "Cincinnati%20Reds",
            "St.%20Louis%20Cardinals"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Sports",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "In%20Formula%201%2C%20the%20Virtual%20Safety%20Car%20was%20introduced%20following%20the%20fatal%20crash%20of%20which%20driver%3F",
        "correct_answer": "Jules%20Bianchi",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Ayrton%20Senna",
            "Ronald%20Ratzenberger",
            "Gilles%20Villeneuve"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Sports",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Which%20of%20the%20following%20Grand%20Slam%20tennis%20tournaments%20occurs%20LAST%3F",
        "correct_answer": "US%20Open",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "French%20Open",
            "Wimbledon",
            "Australian%20Open"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Sports",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "What%20is%20the%20exact%20length%20of%20one%20non-curved%20part%20in%20Lane%201%20of%20an%20Olympic%20Track%3F",
        "correct_answer": "84.39m",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "100m",
            "100yd",
            "109.36yd"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Sports",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Which%20portuguese%20island%20is%20soccer%20player%20Cristiano%20Ronaldo%20from%3F",
        "correct_answer": "Madeira",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Terceira",
            "Santa%20Maria",
            "Porto%20Santo"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Sports",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Who%20won%20the%20%22Champions%20League%22%20in%201999%3F",
        "correct_answer": "Manchester%20United",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Barcelona",
            "Bayern%20Munich",
            "Liverpool"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Sports",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "What%20year%20was%20hockey%20legend%20Wayne%20Gretzky%20born%3F",
        "correct_answer": "1961",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "1965",
            "1959",
            "1963"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Sports",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Which%20of%20the%20following%20pitchers%20was%20named%20National%20League%20Rookie%20of%20the%20Year%20for%20the%202013%20season%3F",
        "correct_answer": "Jose%20Fernandez",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Jacob%20deGrom",
            "Shelby%20Miller",
            "Matt%20Harvey"
        ]
    }
]